[{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678839742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":22485,"timeElapsed":66443},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678849952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":10209,"timeElapsed":76652},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678856992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":7040,"timeElapsed":83693},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678859729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":86430},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678865673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5944,"timeElapsed":92374},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678880158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":14483,"timeElapsed":106858},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678885783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":5625,"timeElapsed":112484},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678899343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":13559,"timeElapsed":126044},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678905380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6035,"timeElapsed":132081},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678924069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":16808,"timeElapsed":150770},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678928477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":155178},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5514,"timeElapsed":160692},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678936631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":163332},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":166210},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678944115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4605,"timeElapsed":170816},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678946693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":173394},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678950992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4297,"timeElapsed":177693},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":179960},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678962257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7769,"timeElapsed":188958},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678965429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3172,"timeElapsed":192130},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4893,"timeElapsed":197024},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3272,"timeElapsed":200296},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678978611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5015,"timeElapsed":205312},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3463,"timeElapsed":208776},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678983865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1790,"timeElapsed":210566},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678986727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":213428},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678988857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":215558},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":8604,"timeElapsed":225128},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":227542},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6096,"timeElapsed":233638},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5957,"timeElapsed":239596},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2037,"timeElapsed":241634},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":245652},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3403,"timeElapsed":249056},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679028057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5701,"timeElapsed":254758},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1412,"timeElapsed":256170},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":8041,"timeElapsed":265176},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2059,"timeElapsed":267236},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679042659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2123,"timeElapsed":269360},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679046353,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":273054},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679048745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":275446},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":277914},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3828,"timeElapsed":281742},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2985,"timeElapsed":284728},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5686,"timeElapsed":290414},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3033,"timeElapsed":293448},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8088,"timeElapsed":302646},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1952,"timeElapsed":304598},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679082120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4222,"timeElapsed":308820},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679086425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4305,"timeElapsed":313126},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679088509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2083,"timeElapsed":315210},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":317270},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1595,"timeElapsed":318866},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2831,"timeElapsed":321698},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1544,"timeElapsed":323242},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5260,"timeElapsed":329314},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2261,"timeElapsed":331576},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":333712},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679109341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2330,"timeElapsed":336042},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679111695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":338396},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2645,"timeElapsed":341042},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1705,"timeElapsed":342748},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2499,"timeElapsed":345248},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3702,"timeElapsed":348951},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":9266,"timeElapsed":359352},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2477,"timeElapsed":361830},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3504,"timeElapsed":365335},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3145,"timeElapsed":368480},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679143709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1929,"timeElapsed":370410},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2408,"timeElapsed":372818},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1271,"timeElapsed":374090},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3642,"timeElapsed":377732},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679153785,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2753,"timeElapsed":380486},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3064,"timeElapsed":383550},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":11333,"timeElapsed":395710},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1665,"timeElapsed":397376},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":399839},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2590,"timeElapsed":402430},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":404622},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679180111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2189,"timeElapsed":406812},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679181685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":408386},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3455,"timeElapsed":411842},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":413632},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5879,"timeElapsed":420314},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1458,"timeElapsed":421772},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":424356},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3525,"timeElapsed":427882},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3550,"timeElapsed":431432},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":433592},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679208317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1425,"timeElapsed":435018},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3341,"timeElapsed":438360},{"subjectID":"gc4f96qr0e","prolificID":"6636e5ffb1e341fa2390a2c0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2cd0734fb9ec0f1c91","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1511,"timeElapsed":439872}]